<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Neelima's Blogs &amp; Articles</title><link>https://blogs.neelimamisra.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Neelima's Blogs &amp; Articles</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 19:43:32 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blogs.neelimamisra.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CDO Confessions Part 2: How to Tell If You’re Set Up to Win?</title><link>https://blogs.neelimamisra.com/posts/cdo-confessions-part-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 19:43:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blogs.neelimamisra.com/posts/cdo-confessions-part-2/</guid><description>In Part 2 of CDO Confessions, we stop glamorizing and start reality checking: are you set up to win or just set up? I share a five-dimension checklist to help you self-assess the true state of your digital playground, governance, culture, tech, power, and value. It’s onion-peeling work (yes, there may be tears), but clarity is power. If you score high, you&amp;rsquo;re cleared for take-off; if not, time to rethink the flight plan.</description></item><item><title>CDO Confessions Part 1: Cracking The Role Code</title><link>https://blogs.neelimamisra.com/posts/cdo-confessions-part-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:16:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blogs.neelimamisra.com/posts/cdo-confessions-part-1/</guid><description>The Chief Digital Officer role sounds glamorous, where business meets tech and magic happens. But in reality? It&amp;rsquo;s a balancing act between transformation dreams, political landmines, and endless firefighting. This blog slices through the hype with stories, frameworks, and a wink of humor to help you survive (and maybe even thrive) in the CDO hot seat.</description></item><item><title>When Data Flows Free: An EU Transformation</title><link>https://blogs.neelimamisra.com/posts/eu-data-transformation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:16:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blogs.neelimamisra.com/posts/eu-data-transformation/</guid><description>&lt;p>My journey with the EU Data Act began during a fascinating conversation with a colleague at a large automotive company. His deep expertise in automotive regulations sparked my curiosity about how this groundbreaking legislation would reshape our industry. As a software architect, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but dive deeper.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>